Step two, what we're going to do here is pick the right quality of paper for our drawing.
Now there's a lot of different paper you can use.
I've drawn thousands of drawings on napkins.
You can on any kind of paper that will hold ink, you can use.
But I found the best paper for my drawings is just plain old--paper I use for my computer to print out with--your plain white sheet of paper, and I've had more results with that.
Now, onion-skin paper holds ink really well, but it doesn't work great for coloring on paper.
So this here holds colored ink really well.
Also I have colored pencils I use, but I find that the ink works better with the pencils than the pencils on paper.
Because you always have to keep sharpening your pencils, and then they break and it smears off and it makes it hard.
So I found that this is the best paper to use for the thing I'm going to be using today.